[
  {
    "question": "01000011 01001111 01000100 01000101",
    "answer": "EQFG"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010000 01010101 01011010 01011010 01001100 01000101",
    "answer": "RWBBNG"
  },
  {
    "question": "01000110 01000101 01010011 01010100",
    "answer": "HGUV"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010000 01001100 01000001 01011001",
    "answer": "RNCA"
  },
  {
    "question": "01001110 01000101 01010010 01010110 01000101",
    "answer": "PGTXG"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010011 01001000 01001001 01000110 01010100",
    "answer": "UJKHV"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010101 01001110 01001001 01001111 01001110",
    "answer": "WPKQP"
  },
  {
    "question": "01000010 01001001 01001110 01000001 01010010 01011001",
    "answer": "DKPCTA"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010001 01010101 01001001 01011010",
    "answer": "SWKB"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010011 01000011 01001111 01010010 01000101",
    "answer": "UEQTG"
  },
  {
    "question": "01001011 01000101 01011001",
    "answer": "MGA"
  },
  {
    "question": "01001111 01010000 01000101 01001110",
    "answer": "QRGP"
  },
  {
    "question": "01000100 01000101 01000011 01001111 01000100 01000101",
    "answer": "FGEQFG"
  },
  {
    "question": "01000111 01000001 01001101 01000101",
    "answer": "ICOG"
  },
  {
    "question": "01001100 01001111 01000111 01001001 01000011",
    "answer": "NQIKE"
  },
  {
    "question": "01000001 01010011 01000011 01001001 01001001",
    "answer": "CUEKK"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010011 01001001 01000111 01001110",
    "answer": "UKIP"
  },
  {
    "question": "01000101 01010110 01000101 01001110 01010100",
    "answer": "GXGPV"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010010 01010101 01001100 01000101 01010011",
    "answer": "TWNGU"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010100 01000101 01000001 01001101",
    "answer": "VGCO"
  },
  {
    "question": "01001000 01000101 01011001 01010011",
    "answer": "JGAU"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010000 01000001 01010011 01010011",
    "answer": "RCUU"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010000 01010101 01011010 01010011 01010100",
    "answer": "RWBUV"
  },
  {
    "question": "01001110 01010001 01010101 01000101 01010011 01010100",
    "answer": "PSWGUV"
  },
  {
    "question": "01000011 01001001 01010000 01001000 01000101 01010010",
    "answer": "EKRJGT"
  },
  {
    "question": "01000001 01000010 01000011",
    "answer": "CDE"
  },
  {
    "question": "01000100 01000101 01010011 01001011",
    "answer": "FGUM"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010010 01001111 01010101 01001110 01000100",
    "answer": "TQWPF"
  },
  {
    "question": "01000110 01001001 01001110 01000100",
    "answer": "HKPF"
  },
  {
    "question": "01001001 01000100 01000101 01000001",
    "answer": "KFGC"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010000 01001100 01000001 01001110",
    "answer": "RNCP"
  },
  {
    "question": "01001100 01000101 01010110 01000101 01001100",
    "answer": "NGXGN"
  },
  {
    "question": "01001101 01000001 01010000",
    "answer": "OCR"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010000 01001111 01001001 01001110 01010100",
    "answer": "RQKPV"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010011 01001000 01001111 01010111",
    "answer": "UJQY"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010000 01000101 01000001 01000011 01000101",
    "answer": "RGCEG"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010000 01000001 01010011 01010011 01001011 01000101 01011001",
    "answer": "RCUUMGA"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010000 01010101 01011010 01011010 01001100 01000101 01010010",
    "answer": "RWBBNGT"
  },
  {
    "question": "01000101 01010011 01000011 01000001 01010000 01000101",
    "answer": "GUECRG"
  },
  {
    "question": "01001000 01001001 01000100 01000101",
    "answer": "JKFG"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010011 01000101 01000001 01010010 01000011 01001000",
    "answer": "UGCTEJ"
  },
  {
    "question": "01000011 01001111 01000100 01000101 01010010",
    "answer": "EQFGT"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010111 01001001 01001110 01001110 01000101 01010010",
    "answer": "YKPPGT"
  },
  {
    "question": "01000101 01010110 01000101 01001110 01010100",
    "answer": "GXGPV"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010100 01010010 01001001 01000011 01001011",
    "answer": "VTKEM"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010011 01010101 01000010 01001110 01000101 01010100",
    "answer": "UWDPGV"
  },
  {
    "question": "01010001 01010101 01000101 01010011 01010100",
    "answer": "SWGUV"
  },
  {
    "question": "01000110 01001111 01010011 01010011",
    "answer": "HQUU"
  },
  {
    "question": "01000001 01001001 01001001 01000100",
    "answer": "CKKF"
  }
]